this video is for all my left-handed
people I see you I care today we're
going to talk about 13 things that only
us left-handed people would understand
so left-handed people only make up about
10 to 12 percent of the population and
let's just say we have a huge learning
curve when it comes to using things in
getting used to things let's talk about
number one scissors scissors seemed like
a really handy dandy tool to have but
frust left-handed people you need to
know the struggle of finding a pair of
left-handed scissors I didn't even know
they made left-handed scissors until I
was like in high school
look at how difficult it can be to
simply cut through a piece of paper and
try to cut a straight line we are forced
to basically hold them upside down if we
can't even find a pair of left-handed
scissors which in my classrooms they
never even had and don't we all know
about the anxiety of walking into a
classroom and seeing these things we all
know that familiar anxiety of scanning
the room really quickly trying to find a
left-handed desk so you either find one
and run to it or you give up and you go
and sit down and a desk that's designed
for a right-handed person and then
you're left kind of your ottoman and
then you have two right there you
position your body weird for the whole
class what about mugs I mean we buy mugs
with these cute sayings and we can't
even see what's on it so there you are
in the morning trying to enjoy a cup of
coffee with a cute saying on it and you
can't even enjoy it but the person
you're drinking coffee with can what
about kyun openers more like deathtrap
thank God for these things can openers
are definitely designed for right you
need people if you try to open it up
with your left hand it's basically
upside down or your left trying to put
it on really awkwardly so you either
learn how to do it with your right hand
or you buy those cans that you can
easily open the lid on it you don't even
realize how often that US left-handed
people have to overcome or a dam what
about jean zippers even jeans are
designed for right-handed people you
have to go in with your right hand open
zipper if you go in with your left hand
it gets real awkward and you have that
flap you have to deal with what about
the struggle of spiral notebooks my
left-handers know what I'm talking about
you walk around with that weird dent in
your hand also what about binders you're
left kind of trying to get in between
the binder or work around it work about
it it's just our what about pens and
pencils we all know how it feels to be
done writing your notes in class and you
lift your hand up and nothing but silver
and then you have to be careful not to
smudge it on yourself on your face on
your clothes while we're talking about
pens or pencils we're about having to
always read an upside-down detail huh
that drives redo it you know and it's
like they don't even want us to enjoy
ice cream when you're right-handed you
just scoop it nicely but when you're
left-handed Oh what do you know you're
putting your hands right in the ice
cream it's pretty much impossible to
scoop out the struggle I left a nurse
now what about video games controllers
are definitely made for right unit
people so us left-handers have no choice
but to overcome and learn how to
kick-ass a little bit better than right
unit people what about your mouse and
your mousepad when you walk to the
computer and it's always on the
right-hand side you have two options
people you can either adjust it over to
the left-hand side or you can just get
used to using it on the right side it's
like stores don't even want to take our
credit cards awkward what do you have to
do you have to put it in your right hand
and you have to swipe before you write
you the people watching who don't
believe me you try to take your credit
card and swipe it with the left hand
measuring cups
hope you like reading the metric system
will help you guys like my list of 13
things that only left-handed people
would understand from my right-handed
people out there that are watching this
video I'm going to challenge you why
don't you hit that like or subscribe
button with your left hand I will see
you in the next video walk a mile in my
shoes there's only like 10 or 12 percent
of us left-handed people on the earth
almost extinct see I thought you had it
bad I am not only left-handed but I'm
also redhead and I've got green eyes I
think I'm one of a kind you want to
throw somebody off shake their hand with
your left hand awkward because everyone
is used to shaking hands with the right
hand
hello yeah I dare you the next time you
shake someone's hand to shake it with
your left hand now look at their
attention hashtag left hand challenge